publicdomainvectors.org 2014-11-20

# Privacy policy | Public domain vectors

  * [Home]() /
  * Privacy policy

Personal information 

We **do not** sell or otherwise provide Personal Information to other companies for the marketing of their own products or services. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide You services or as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

We reserve the right to disclose your Personal Information as required by law (e.g., to comply with a subpoena, warrant, or court order) and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, avoid litigation, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, and/or respond to a government request. We may also disclose information about You if we determine that such disclosure should be made for reasons of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance.

IP Addresses

When you access our website, our website servers register the type of web browsers that you are using and your IP address. An IP address is a number assigned to your computer by a Web server when you're on the Web. We collect IP addresses to obtain aggregate information on the use of Publicdomainvectors.org. We only use the information we find out from tracking IP addresses in the aggregate, such as how many users entered a specific area of our site, and not to track a specific IP address to identify an individual user. However, we may use such information to identify a user if we feel that there are or may be safety and/or security issues or to comply with legal requirements.

Links

Publicdomainvectors.org may contain links to other websites. These sites may have separate and independent privacy policies for which Publicdomainvectors.org is not responsible for. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.

Advertising

Advertisements that appear on Publicdomainvectors.org are sometimes served directly to users by third party advertisers. These third party ad services may use cookies, web beacons, clear .gifs or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness. In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. Occasionally, as part of advertising programs, third-party advertisers may collect personally identifiable information, such as email address and name, for promotional and advertising activities.

Publicdomainvectors.org does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers.

Your consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

Changes to this policy

If we decide to change this policy, we will post those changes on this page.

This policy was last modified on 10/15/2013
